Listen, sir, for the last time, I don't care what the computer says.
聽著，先生，我最後一次告訴你 我不在乎電腦上登記了什麼
We did not take a bag of Mashuga Nuts from the minibar.
我們沒有從房間冰箱 拿走一包糖果
And we did not watch Dr. Do-Me-A-Little.
我們沒有看《熱心助人的醫生》
-Joey, were you in our room last night? -No.
-喬伊，昨晚你到過我們房間？ -沒有
I was told the name of the movie would not appear on the bill.
他們說電影片名 不會出現在帳單上
-We're checking out of the bridal suite. -That's right, I'm no longer a bride.
-我們要退掉新房了 -沒錯，我不再是新娘
I'll never be a bride again. Now I'm just someone's wife.
我永遠都當不了新娘 現在我是某人的太太
And I'm the happiest guy in the world.
現在我是全世界最快樂的男人
Honey, don't be upset. We still have so much to look forward to.
甜心，別難過 我們還是有很光明的未來
Yeah, right.
對
-We got the honeymoon. -That's not till Thursday.
-我們還要去度蜜月 -那是星期四的事
-The wedding pictures. -It won't be ready for weeks.
-還有婚紗照 -那得等上好幾個星期
Not the disposable cameras from the tables.
但婚宴上用即可拍 拍的照片馬上可以洗好
That's true. I knew I married you for a reason!
沒錯 我就知道我嫁給你是有原因的
Tell you what, I will go get them developed, and you can go home.
聽著，我拿照片去洗 你先回家吧
-What? What did you take a picture of? -Nothing.
-什麼？你拍了什麼？ -沒什麼
It was something.
一定很精彩
Ross has the cameras. Has he checked out yet?
即可拍在羅斯那裡 他還沒有退房嗎？
Are you joking? Checkout is not till noon.
你在開玩笑嗎？ 退房時間是中午
-And he has a good 11 minutes left. -So?
-他還有11分鐘 -所以呢？
So Ross had never checked out of a room a minute before he had to.
羅斯從來不會 提早退房
One time, when we were dating, we got a late checkout.
我們在交往的時候 有一次延後退房
He got so excited, it was the best sex we ever had.
他非常興奮 那是我們最棒的性經驗
Until he screamed out "Radisson" at the end.
直到他最後 大叫著「拉迪森」
Okay, well, I'm gonna get Ross, get the cameras and get them developed.
好吧，我去找羅斯拿照相機 然後把底片拿去洗
32, Joe. You're 32!
喬伊，你32歲了
-Here's a copy of your bill. -Thanks.
-這是你的帳單 -謝謝
Champagne, strawberries..
香檳，草莓…
Oh, my God! I can't believe Chandler ordered porn on our wedding night.
天啊，我不敢相信 錢德在我們的新婚之夜看黃色電影
Yeah, that's sad. Mashuga Nut?
對，那真的很慘 糖果？
The One With The Red Sweater
本集播出：紅色毛衣
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
I have six minutes left!
我還有六分鐘
It's me.
是我
Soaps, shampoos. Are you really taking all this stuff?
肥皂，洗髮精 你真的要把這些東西帶走？
Why not? It's built into the price of the room.
為什麼不行？ 這全包含在房費裡
Yeah, but you don't need.. What is this?
對，但你不需要… 這是什麼？
Thread.
針線包
Score!
答對了
-Where are the disposable cameras? -What cameras?
-即可拍在哪裡？ -什麼即可拍？
-Last night I asked you to take them. -No, you didn't.
-昨晚我把它們交給你 -才沒有
Yes, remember? Right before we cut the cake, I said..
就是有，記得嗎？ 在切蛋糕前我說…
Yeah, you asked me if I could do you a favor.
對，你問我 能不能幫你一個忙
Then my Uncle Murray came up to you and handed you a check.
這時墨瑞叔叔走過來 交給你一張支票
Then you said, "Why is it called a check? Why not a Yugoslavian?"
然後你說「它為什麼叫做支票？ 為什麼不叫南斯拉夫人？」
Then you did that, and my Uncle Murray looked at me like:
然後你那麼做 墨瑞叔叔這樣看著我
-So you don't have the cameras? -No, sorry.
-即可拍不在你手上？ -沒錯，抱歉
So, what? They're gone? Monica's gonna freak!
什麼？相機不見了？ 摩妮卡會氣瘋的
I'm sure they're here somewhere. I'll help you look.
我相信它們應該就在某個地方 我幫你找
-Great. -In three minutes.
-太棒了 -再等三分鐘
Are you gonna open the presents without Chandler?
你要丟下錢德 自己拆禮物？
No! I'm just..
不，我只是…
They're calling out to me. This little guy even crawled up in my lap.
它們在呼換我 這個小傢伙甚至爬到我的膝蓋上
Chandler wouldn't mind if I opened just one present. What do you think it is?
錢德不會介意我拆開一樣禮物 你覺得它是什麼？
A little mirror that, when you look into it..
是一面小鏡子 只要你一照它…
you see yourself as an old woman.
你會發現自己變成了老太婆
A tiny salt shaker!
是一個迷你鹽罐
Oh, my God, for tiny salt!
天啊，是用來裝迷你鹽的
Oh, wow! Okay. Well, that was fun. That was fun.
好吧，那真的很好玩 很好玩
Okay, I'll just wait for Chandler to open up the rest of them.
我會等錢德 一起拆開其他禮物
Although, you know, this is part of a salt-and-pepper set.
但這只是調味瓶組的 一部份
It may just count as only half a present. What do you think?
或許它只算半項禮物 你覺得呢？
I guess it's okay to open one more if it's part of a set. It's probably this one.
我猜如果它是一套的，再拆開一樣 應該沒關係，或許是這個
Or this one!
或是這個
-How are you? Got any morning sickness? -The guys don't know yet, do they?
-你好嗎？會害喜嗎？ -男生們還不知道吧？
Joey and Ross don't know anything. Chandler thinks Phoebe's pregnant.
喬伊跟羅斯什麼都不知道 錢德認為是菲比懷孕了
That's right. Chandler does still think I'm pregnant.
沒錯 錢德還是以為我懷孕了
He hasn't asked me how I'm feeling or offered to carry my bags.
他沒有問我感覺如何 也沒有幫我提袋子
I feel bad for the woman who ends up with him.
我為跟他在一起的女人 覺得難過
After you, of course.
我是指在你之後的女人
Don't worry. You only have to be pregnant for a few more hours..
別擔心，你只需要 再假裝懷孕幾小時…
because I'm telling the father today.
因為今天我要告訴孩子的爸
Is it someone in the building? That tall guy on the first floor?
他就住在這棟公寓嗎？ 是一樓那個高個兒嗎？
-No! -What? I think he's cute.
-不 -什麼？我覺得他很可愛
-Then you have his baby. -Believe me, I'm trying.
-那麼你可以去懷他的孩子 -相信我，我正在努力
It's so weird. You're gonna tell this guy today..
這真的好奇怪 你今天要告訴這個男人…
and he has no idea what's gonna happen.
他不知道 會發生什麼事
You're just gonna knock on his door and change his life forever.
你要敲敲他的門 永遠地改變他的一生
You're like Ed McMahon, except without the big check.
你就像艾德麥馬漢 只不過手上沒有拿大額支票
Or the raw sexual magnetism.
也沒有原始的性吸引力
Yeah, well, I guess it is pretty big news.
對，我猜 那是個大消息
Pretty big? It's huge! God, this guy doesn't have a clue.
大消息？它是超級大消息 天啊，這個男人什麼都不知道
He's just walking down the street thinking, "I had sex with Rachel Greene. I rock!"
他走在街上心想 「我跟瑞秋葛林做愛，太帥了」
Then, bam! He's a father, everything's different.
然後，碰，他當了爸爸 一切都不一樣了
It's only different if he wants it to be. I'm not gonna ask him for anything.
除非他真的想當爸爸 我不會對他提出任何要求
He still has this huge decision to make.
他還是得做出 重大的決定
Now he's walking around thinking, "Do I want to be a dad?" Then, bam!
現在他邊走邊想 「我要當爸爸嗎？」然後，碰
What was that "bam"?
這次怎麼了？
I don't know. He's hit by a bus, or something.
我不知道 他可能是撞上巴士了
Joey, what would you do if someone you slept with told you she was pregnant?
喬伊，如果跟你上過床的女人 告訴你她懷孕了，你會怎麼辦？
Who called here?
誰打電話到這裡來？
Did she sound blond? Did she have an accent? I gotta make a call.
她聽起來像金髮美女嗎？她有口音嗎？ 我得去打個電話
Should have never walked into that Sunglass Hut!
我不該到 那家太陽眼鏡專賣店的
It's not you! You didn't get anybody pregnant.
不是你 你沒有讓任何人懷孕
Why would you scare me like that? What the hell's going on?
你為什麼要那樣子嚇我？ 發生了什麼事？
Is somebody pregnant?
有人懷孕了嗎？
Oh, yeah! That's me.
對，我懷孕了
Oh, my God, Pheebs! You're gonna have a baby?
天啊，菲比 你要生孩子了？
Yes, I am. Oh, my God, I'm gonna have a baby!
對 天啊，我要生孩子了
-Wait a minute, who's the father? -You don't know him.
-等一下，孩子的爸是誰？ -你不認識他
It's not important. He wants nothing to do with me or the baby.
那不重要 他不希望跟我或孩子扯上關係
Who is this guy? Because I will track him down and kick his ass!
這傢伙是誰？ 因為我要把他找出來，痛扁他一頓
-David Linn. -David Linn!
-大衛林恩 -大衛林恩
-Who's David Linn? -Some guy from my gym. Little annoying.
-誰是大衛林恩？ -我在健身房認識的人，他很討厭
-Chandler? -Did you find the cameras?
-錢德 -你找到即可拍了嗎？
-No. Did you? -Yes.
-沒有，你呢？ -我找到了
That's why I'm under the table, celebrating.
那就是我躲在桌下的原因 我想要慶祝
I checked in the lost and found. I talked to the manager. No one's turned them in.
我去失物中心問過管理員 沒有人撿到即可拍
Great. Those cameras were the only thing that was gonna cheer Monica up today.
太棒了，今天只有那些即可拍 能讓摩妮卡打起精神來
You just got married. Why is she so depressed?
你們剛剛結婚 她為什麼要心情不好？
All my energy is going into not asking that question.
我沒有力氣 問她那個問題
-I can't believe I screwed this up! -I'm sorry, man.
-我不敢相信我搞砸了 -我很遺憾，兄弟
Here's a thought. This is the same ballroom.
我有個點子 你們在這個宴會廳請客
There's a band. There's gonna be plenty of dressed-up people.
這裡有樂隊 等一下會有很多人盛裝前來
Are you suggesting we dance our troubles away?
你建議 我們可以丟下問題不管？
No, I'm saying we buy more of these at the gift shop..
不，我是說我們到禮品店 買一些即可拍…
throw our tuxes back on and take a few pictures.
換上禮服 拍幾張照片
We just have to make sure not to get anybody's faces.
我們只要 不拍到任何人的臉
Are you serious?
你是認真的嗎？
I'm thinking about your new bride at home.
我想到 在家等你的新娘
Do you want to start your life together by letting her down?
你想在你們共度一生的第一天 就讓她失望嗎？
Marriage advice? Really?
你真的要給我關於婚姻的建議？
I'm telling you, this looks exactly like your wedding.
我是在告訴你 這看起來很像你的婚宴
-Aren't these the same flowers? -I don't know. Monica picked them.
-這些花都一樣吧？ -我不知道，花是摩妮卡挑的
-What about the chairs? -Those too.
-椅子呢？ -也是
-The place settings? -Her.
-佈置呢？ -她挑的
-What did you do? -I was in charge of the cameras.
-你做了什麼？ -我負責看好照相機
Gift shop?
禮品店？
-Did you do it yet? -Not yet.
-你說了嗎？ -還沒有
Then what are you doing here? Are you about to do it?
那麼你在這裡做什麼？ 你真的要說嗎？
Is it Gunther?
是阿甘嗎？
-It's not Gunther! -Thank God. Because that hair on a baby?
-不是阿甘 -謝天謝地，還好寶寶不會有他的頭髮
The father is not here, okay? I haven't told him yet.
孩子的爸不在這裡，好嗎？ 我還沒有告訴他
-I don't think I can tell him at all now. -Why not?
-我想現在我沒辦法告訴他 -為什麼？
I was walking down the street, thinking, "I'm gonna tell the father." And then, bam!
我在街上邊走邊想 「我要告訴孩子的爸」，然後，碰
Bus?
你撞到了巴士？
No, you! You freaked me out. You kept saying how huge this all is.
不，是你，你嚇了我一跳 你一直在提醒我這是件大事
But it is huge.
但它的確是件大事
I know. But I was just thinking about how huge it was for me.
我知道，我只是在想 它對我來說有多重要
I didn't even go to how huge it'll be for the father.
我根本不知道 這對孩子的爸來說有多重要
You're thinking about this way too much. Just tell him and get it over with.
你想太多了 告訴他，把事情做個了斷
It's like ripping off this Band-Aid, quick and painless. Watch.
它就像撕掉OK繃一樣 越快越不痛，你看
Oh, mother of..!
天殺的…
See?
看吧？
-Are we opening presents? -No. I shouldn't have even opened these.
-我們要拆禮物了嗎？ -不，我根本不該拆開禮物
Joey, I am out of control! You have to do me a favor.
喬伊，我控制不了自己 你得幫我一個忙
No matter what I say, no matter what I do..
不論我說什麼 不論我做什麼…
please, do not let me open another present. Okay?
拜託，不要讓我 再拆開任何禮物，好嗎？
Give me one more.
再給我一個禮物
Oh, good, you're here. Pheebs? Listen..
很好，你來了 菲比，聽我說…
-Sit down, I got something I wanna say. -All right.
-坐下，我要告訴你一件事 -好吧
It's a scary world out there, especially for a single mom.
外面的世界很可怕 特別是對單親媽媽來說
I've always felt that you and I have a special bond.
我一直覺得 我跟你之間很特別
So..
所以…
Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
菲比布非，你願意嫁給我嗎？
Oh, my God!
我的天啊
Oh, yeah, I'll marry you.
我願意嫁給你
-You can't marry him! -Hey, lady, your day's over. It's my turn.
-你不能嫁給他 -小姐，你結過婚了，這次輪到我
-Why can't she marry me? -I can and I will.
-她為什麼不能嫁給我？ -我可以，我也願意
She's not pregnant. Rachel's the one who's pregnant.
她沒有懷孕 是瑞秋懷孕了
Oh, my God!
天啊
He'd notice when you didn't have a baby in nine months!
九個月後你生不出孩子 他會發現的
It's Joey!
他是喬伊
I love you.
我愛你
Wait, I can't believe it! Rachel's pregnant? Who's the father?
等一下，我不敢相信 瑞秋懷孕了？孩子的爸是誰？
We don't know.
我們不知道
-I wonder if it's that dude. -There's a dude?
-不知道是不是那個傢伙 -哪個傢伙？
Who is it?
是誰呢？
About a month ago this guy spent the night with Rachel.
大約一個月前 這傢伙跟瑞秋共度春宵
I didn't see who it was, but..
我沒有看到他，但是…
Was that story over?
他把故事說完了嗎？
The guy left this.
那個傢伙留下這個
Oh, my God! I know who the father is.
天啊 我知道孩子的爸是誰
People have got to finish their stories.
說故事的人 得把故事說完
Hello.
哈囉
I don't know if we're both in. Come closer.
我不知道我們有沒有都照進去 靠近一點
Nice aftershave.
你的古龍水味道很好聞
If you want some, I've got eight mini bottles in my bag.
如果你想來一點 我包包裡有八罐隨身瓶
-Excuse me, could you take a picture of us? -Of course.
-對不起，你能幫我們拍照嗎？ -沒問題
Would you take one of us?
你能幫我們照一張嗎？
Yeah, sure.
沒問題
Click.
喀
-It didn't click. -I heard it.
-我沒有聽到快門聲 -我聽到了
-But there was no flash. -Why won't you take our picture?
-但閃光燈沒亮 -你為什麼不幫我們拍照？
Oh, yeah. I'll take your picture.
對，我會幫你們拍照
Your finger was covering the lens.
你的手指擋到鏡頭了
Who are you, Ansel Adams? Get out of here!
你是安瑟亞當斯嗎？ 快滾吧
（中央咖啡廳）
Look, I feel really bad about how I freaked you out before..
聽著，我真的很難過 之前我嚇壞你了…
so I asked the father to meet you here so you could tell him.
所以我請孩子的爸到裡面等你 你可以告訴他事實
What? Wait a minute. How do you even know who the father is?
什麼？等一下 你怎麼知道孩子的爸是誰？
I may play the fool at times..
或許有時候我傻傻的…
but I'm more than a pretty blond girl with an ass that won't quit.
但事實上我是個勇不放棄的 金髮美女
I believe this belongs to the father of your baby..
我相信 這是孩子爸的衣服…
Oh, God. He's in there right now?
天啊，他就在裡面？
You can turn around, or you can go rip the Band-Aid off. What do you want to do?
你可以轉身離開或是長痛不如短痛 你打算怎麼做？
-Let's rip. -Are you sure?
-我們把事情做個了斷吧 -你確定？
-Phoebe! -Okay. Sorry.
-菲比 -好吧，抱歉
Hey, Rach.
瑞秋
Why don't you go up on-stage. I'll get a picture of you doing the speech.
你為什麼不到台上呢？ 我要拍張你說話時的照片
Will the owner of a 1995 Buick LeSabre please see the front desk?
1995年別克李薩布利的車主 請跟櫃檯聯絡
Your car is about to be towed.
你的車就要被拖走了
That's my car!
那是我的車
-A '95 LeSabre? -Yes.
-1995年的李薩布利？ -對
-A green LeSabre? -Yes!
-綠色的李薩布利？ -對
-I'm sorry, I meant a blue LeSabre. -Yes, green-blue.
-抱歉，我是說藍色的李薩布利 -對，我的車是藍綠色的
Well, go. Go move it!
快去把它移開吧
Ready for the last picture? Get ready to run.
準備要拍最後一張照片了嗎？ 拍完馬上就跑
Congratulations on your wedding.
恭喜
So, what's this about?
這是怎麼一回事？
Rachel has something she wants to tell you.
瑞秋有事 要告訴你
And I believe that this is your red sweater.
我相信 這是你的紅毛衣
No, this is my red sweater.
不，這才是我的紅毛衣
Oh, no.
不
Could I get anyone a coffee?
有人要喝咖啡嗎？
Or poison? No? Just for me? Okay.
或是毒藥？沒有嗎？只有我要？好吧
What's going on, Rach?
發生了什麼事？瑞秋
Nothing. Phoebe kind of made a mistake.
沒事 菲比弄錯了
But you do wear that sweater a lot. Are you involved in some kind of dare?
但你的確常穿那件毛衣 你在做什麼冒險的事嗎？
I'm actually glad Phoebe called.
事實上我很高興能接到菲比的電話
I know we broke up because you thought I was immature, but I've grown up.
我知道我們會分手是因為你覺得 我太幼稚，但我已經長大了
I think we should get back together.
我想我們應該復合
It's just not the right time.
時機不對
It is the right time. I'm ready for more.
時機非常恰當 我做了萬全的準備
Come on, Rach. Let's give it another try.
來吧，瑞秋 我們可以再試一次
I'm having a baby.
我懷孕了
-You can go. -Thank you.
-你可以走了 -謝謝
I don't know how any of these got opened!
我不知道 禮物怎麼會是打開的
-You opened them all? -I know, I am a terrible person.
-你拆開了所有的禮物？ -我知道，我是個可怕的人
Chandler's never gonna trust me with anything ever again.
錢德永遠都不會 再相信我任何事
You got my parents' gift.
你拆開了我爸媽的禮物
-What is that? -I think it does something to salami.
-那是什麼？ -應該是跟意大利臘腸有關的東西
-How'd it go? -What did Tag say?
-情況如何？ -泰格怎麼說？
Tag is not the father. And Joey knows now?
泰格不是孩子的爸 喬伊知道了？
I do, Rach, I do. And I am so happy for you.
我知道了，瑞秋 我為你感到高興
Wow, you didn't even try to unhook my bra.
你沒有試著 要解開我的胸罩
-So are you ever gonna tell whoever it is? -I will. I'm just not up for it tonight.
-你要告訴孩子的爸嗎？ -我會的，只是今晚我不想那麼做
No matter what this guy says, you're not gonna be alone in this.
不論這傢伙說什麼 你不會獨自面對這一切
-I'm not? -No. Listen..
-是嗎？ -不，聽著…
It's a scary world out there, especially for a single mom.
外面的世界很可怕 特別是對單親媽媽來說
I've always felt like you and I have this special bond, you know?
我一直覺得 我跟你之間很特別
-Rachel Greene, will you marry me? -What?
-瑞秋葛林，你願意嫁給我嗎？ -什麼？
-What? -What?!
-什麼？ -什麼？
-Pheebs, give me the ring back. -No!
-菲比，把戒指還給我 -不
Joey, you're so sweet, so sweet, honey. But I'm not looking for a husband.
喬伊，你真的很體貼 但我不要一個丈夫
I understand.
我瞭解
Well, if you'll excuse me, I'm going to go and lie down.
對不起 我想去躺一下
喬伊
What? I proposed to you. It balances out.
什麼？我跟你求過婚 這樣才公平
I can't say that didn't hurt.
我不能說我不心痛
But I'll take you back, Joey Tribbiani.
但我會原諒你，喬伊崔比亞尼
-Listen, about that, I only offered.. -Ooh, a Salami Buddy!
-聽著，我只是說… -意大利臘腸用具
There you go!
來吧
-We're back! -Great.
-我們回來了 -太棒了
We're hanging in the kitchen. Let's stay in the kitchen.
我們待在廚房吧 待在廚房就好了
-It's picture time. -You're gonna love these.
-現在是看照片時間 -你一定會喜歡的
Here's a picture of Ross.
這是羅斯的照片
And that's me.
那是我
And that's me and Ross.
我跟羅斯
And here's a picture of our first kiss as a married couple.
這是我們第一次 以新婚夫妻身份接吻的照片
Wow, that is a great picture. Yeah!
那張照片真的很棒
And interesting, because I found the cameras in one of our bags.
真的太有趣了 因為我在我們的行李裡找到即可拍
Didn't see that coming.
我沒想到這一點
So this isn't a picture of our first kiss..
這不是 我們第一次接吻的照片…
but it is a picture of my first kiss with this lady.
但它的確是 我跟這位女士第一次接吻的照片
Which, by the look on your face, I'm sure you'll remember, so there's no need..
從你臉上的表情看來 我相信你會記得，所以我不必…
-I'll take the real pictures to get developed. -Good idea.
-我會拿真的底片去洗 -好主意
You opened all the presents without me? We were gonna do that together.
你不管我自己拆開所有禮物？ 我們說好要一起拆的
You kissed another woman?!
你吻了另一個女人？
-Call it even? -Okay.
-我們扯平了？ -好吧
-I'm gonna go get these in some water. -You stole those from that wedding?
-我要把花插到花瓶裡 -你偷走了那個婚禮的花？
No, the hotel lobby. They think they can charge me for some dirty movie..
不，這是飯店大廳的花 他們以為能超收我黃色電影…
and a bag of Mashuga Nuts, they got another thing coming!
還有一袋糖果的錢 我一定要討回公道
Hey, my sweater!
我的毛衣
I've been looking for this for, like, a month.
我找這件毛衣 找了一個月
Oh, my God!
我的天啊
-Hey, how you doing? -Good. Long time no see.
-你好嗎？ -我很好，好久不見
-Like your sweater. -Right back at you.
-我喜歡你的毛衣 -我也是
-It's crazy about Rachel. -Well, she's one crazy lady.
-瑞秋的事真的太瘋狂了 -她一直都瘋瘋癲癲的
-So whose is it? -I don't know, some Italian guy.
-到底是誰的呢？ -我不知道，應該是個意大利人吧
Come on, read your own label. See you later. He is so weird.
少來了，看看你自己的標籤 後會有期，他真是奇怪